question_data = [
    {
        "question": """[white]Darth Vader tells you he's your father. What do you do?:\n[/]
        [black]A. Kill him and take his place\n
        B. Try and convince him to turn to the good side of the force
        [/]""",
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": "",
    },
    {
        "question": """[white]a co-worker is gossiping about you,how do you handle it?
        [/]
        [black]A. Introduce them to a left hook\n
        B. Ignore it\n""",
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": "",
    },
    {
        "question": """[white]Would you rather talk like Yoda or breathe like Darth Vader?\n
        [black]A. Talk like Yoda\n
        B. Breathe like Darth Vader\n""",
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "incorrect_answers": "",
    },
    {
        "question": """[white]How do you handle road rage when somone cuts you off?\n
        [black]A. Cut them off too so they get a taste of thier own medicine\n
        B. Practice taking deep breaths whenever some one cut you off\n""",
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": "",
    },
    {
        "question": """[white]Your due for a new starfighter,
        what catches your eye when you get to the shipyard:\n
        [black]A. TIE/x1 starfighter\n
        B. T65 X-wing starfighter\n""",
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": "",
    },
    {
        "question": """[white]You find a wallet on the sidewalk filled with cash,
        What do you do?:\n
        [black]A. Send the wallet back to the owner\n
        B. Send the wallet back to the owner but keep the money\n""",
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": "",
    },
    {
        "question": """[white]You are exhausted from marking terminal app assignments
        and decide to book a holiday. What destination do you choose?\n
        [black]A. planet of Sorgan. A world dotted by ramshackle villages
        where farmers spend their days fishing for krill in the wetlands,\n
        B. Planet Mustafar, a lava planet, full of volcanoes and  mines.\n""",
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "incorrect_answers": "",
    },
    {
        "question": """[white]Would you rather get a tattoo of Jar-Jar Binks on your neck,
        or be woken up every morning by being slapped in the face?\n
        [black]A. Slapped in the face\n
        B. Tattoo \n""",
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "incorrect_answers": "",
    },
    {
        "question": """[white]Would you rather be frozen in carbonite or serve under Darth Vader?\n
        [black]A. Serve under Darth Vader\n
        B. Frozen in carbonite\n""",
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": "",
    },
    {
        "question": """[white]Would you rather have a drink on the Death Star bar,
        or the bar at Mos Eisley?\n
        [black]A. Death Star bar\n
        B. Mos Eisley bar\n""",
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": "",
    },
]

quest_data = [
    {
        "question": """ You arrive at the Jedi temple on the ice planet of Ilum
        to seek a Kyber crystal so you can build your light sabre.
        You hear a song playing in the distance. What do you do?\n
        [black]A. You trust your instincts and Follow the sound.\n
        B. ignore it and Walk in the opposite direction \n""",
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "incorrect_answers": """You walk in the opposit direction
        slip over and die """,
    },
    {
        "question": """ You get to the source of the music, and you notice it's a kyber crystal,
        then suddenly, you see a giant Rancor crawling out from a cave
        What do you do?\n
        [black]A. You run and hide behind the nearest rock in the cave\n
        B. You realize it's the kyber crystal,
        and it is testing you to overcome your fear,
        so you charge at the rancor\n""",
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": """[black bold] You start running,
        but the rancor catches you and kills you instantly """,
    },
    {
        "question": """ When you get close to the rancor it disappears,
        so you grab the kyber crystal and realise you have to escape the
        ice cave before the entrance freezes shut.
        You start running back to where you came from, and you get to a fork
        in the cave, and you can't remember which way.
        What do you do?\n
        [black]A. Go left\n
        B. Go right\n""",
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": """[black bold] You get to the end of the cave,
        and you realise it was the wrong way.
        The cave entrance has frozen over. You freeze to death """,
    },
    {
        "question": """ Years later...... you are on a mission with your Jedi master
        where you have to meet with Trade Federation Viceroy
        to discuss a trivial trade dipute.
        While waiting in a room on the Commanding Viceroy ship,
        you notice Dioxis gas coming out of the vents, and then the room locks.
        What do you do?\n
        [black]A. just crack a window in the ship
        let the gas seep out into space\n
        B. hold you breath for long as you can
        until they think you are dead\n""",
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": """[black bold] You crack a window open with your light sabre
        and instantly get sucked into space a suffocate """,
    },
    {
        "question": """ The doors open, and you race out with your master and
        destroy all enemy droids in your way.
        You reach the room that the Commanding Viceroy is in,
        but the blast doors close and lock you out.
        Then you notice destroyer droids roll in and start shooting at you.
        What do you do?\n
        [black]A. Their shields are too strong,
        so you use your Jedi speed and escape\n
        B. you stand your ground you cant let the Commanding Viceroy get away
        with trying to kill you and your master\n""",
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "incorrect_answers": """[black bold] The shields on the battle droids are
        too strong you and your master are killed. """,
    },
]

darth_data = [
    {
        "question": """ your master sends you on a mission to hunt
        and kill  Jedi Master Kirak Infil'a  to claim  his
        kyber crystal so you can build your sith light sabre
        do you accept the mission\n
        [black]A. yes\n
        B. no \n""",
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "incorrect_answers": """[black bold] your master calls you a tratior
        and kills you""",
    },
    {
        "question": """ you find  Jedi Master Kirak Infil'a on river moon of Al'doleem
        and draw him out by flooding the village,
        while he is distracted helping people in the village,
        you grab his light sabre
        and hold it to his neck. What do you do?\n
        [black]A. you ask any last words, Jedi, before i take your life\n
        B. you don't hesitate or waste time and end
        Master Kirak Infil'a life """,
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": """Jedi Master Kirak Infil'a uses the force and
        pushes you away you land on your head and  break your neck """,
    },
    {
        "question": """ you grab  the kyber crystal and jump on your ship to hed
        back to your master and realise you will be passing the planet zeltros
        also known as the party planet, what do you do?\n
        [black]A. decide you need to celebrate
        before you return to your master\n
        B. you decide maybe another time """,
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "incorrect_answers": """[black bold] you go and party but run into a
        Jedi who defeats and captures you""",
    },
    {
        "question": """ you get back to your master and tell him the good news
        and he asks to see the kyber crytal what do you do\n
        [black]A. show him the kyber crystal\n
        B. tell him to jam it and say i dont need you anymore
        i am going solo\n""",
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "incorrect_answers": "[black bold] your master kills you ",
    },
    {
        "question": """your master is happy with your obedience and asks you to neal
        before him, what do you do\n
        [black]A. neal before your master so he can give you a sith name\n
        B. tell him you got a sore back from the last mission\n""",
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "incorrect_answers": "[black bold] your master kills you ",
    },
]
